我欲为人 上季回顾
Last season on Being Human...
我想永远和你在一起
I want to be with you forever.
当爱情再次来敲门
When love finds you again,
你不会逃避
you will not run from it.
我不会假装我们之间
I'm not gonna pretend
什么都没有发生
that what happened between us didn't mean anything.
我希望你把我也转化成吸血鬼
I want you to turn me in what you are.
你到底做了什么
What did you do?
快跑
Run!
我爱你
I love you.
-事情有变 -我看见了一个幻象
- Something's different. - I had a vision.
我的狼 他依然和我在一起
My wolf. He's still with me.
Josh
Josh?
你不属于这个空间
You don't belong in this plane.
-我绝对不要回到灵狱 -对，你不会
- I'm not going back to limbo. - No, you're not.
你说我们被联系在一起 我要把你一起带走 我要把你留在那
You said we're linked, I'll take you with me, I'll leave you there.
-你不知道我到底能做出什么 -不，我知道
- You don't know what I can do. - Oh no, I do.
Sally
Sally?
是你拿了那本杂志吗
Did you take the magazine?
-你把它放哪了 -嘘
- Where did you put the magazine? - Shhh!
好吧
Oh. OK.
我们还在享受自我时光 是吧
We're still having a "me" time, huh?
你至少应该安排一些美疗项目
You should at least schedule some treatments.
我是说 既然我们都已经在这儿了
I mean, since we're here.
嘘
Shhh...
你不能把杂志拿走又不让我做盐浴
You can't take the magazine and not let me have a salt scrub.
Nora
Nora!
他的速度更快了
He's getting faster!
他受伤了
He's hurt!
他很好
He's fine!
人家都去意大利度蜜月
Some people go to Italy for their honeymoon.
我却用一只羊引诱我老公
I bait my husband with a goat.
明天换我来轮班吧
I'm gonna pick up that shift tomorrow.
谢谢
Thank you.
我路过房子顺便倒垃圾
I stopped by the house and took out the trash.
-我们就只有这些血袋了吗 -是的
- This the only blood we have? - Yeah.
当你在家的时候 有没有看见Sally的任何迹象
When you were at the house, did you see any sign of Sally?
没有 也许她看我们都不在就 我也不知道
No. Maybe she saw we weren't there and... I don't know.
她能去多远
How far can she travel?
我想是任何地方 不是吗
I guess anywhere, really, right?
-也许她驾鹤西去了 -都已经是鬼魂了还怎么驾鹤西去
- Well, maybe she's gone for good. - How can a ghost be gone for good?
方法很多
Lots of ways.
是他伤害的你吗
Did he do that to you?
别管这个了 这早就愈合了
Yeah, forget it, it's, um, it's already healing, so...
你真觉得他越来越快了吗
And you really think he's getting faster?
是啊 但是你知道吗
Yeah, but you know what?
我只需要开始时更领先一点
I just need a bigger head start.
你看 现在他比我更了解这森林
See, he knows these woods better than I do by now.
拜托
Come on!
都已经过了三个月了
It's been 3 months.
这种事一定会发生的
It was bound to happen.
和他一起跑的时候 你觉得他知道吗
When you're running him, do you think he knows?
他知道跑的那个是你吗
Does it still seem like he knows it's you?
是的 当然
Yeah, absolutely.
Josh依然在那里
Josh is still in there.
Aiden 你必须一天三次的跑过他
Aiden, you have to run him 3 times a day
这能使他足够冷静以便把他关起来
just to calm him down enough to get him back in the shed.
你在期待什么呢 Nora 他被困住了
What do you expect? Nora, the guy is trapped,
他很害怕很恐慌
and he's scared and he's panicked.
-我是说 想象一下如果你也变成这样 -我知道 我想象过
- I mean, imagine what it would be... - I know! I try to.
每次我变身的时候都会想
Every time I turn,
如果太阳升起后我没有
I try to imagine what would happen if the sun came up
变回人身将发生什么事
and I wasn't me again.
但是我从来没想出答案
But I never get that far.
因为当你是狼的时候 你不能思考别的事
Because when you're the wolf, you can't imagine anything else.
-我们会让他恢复原样的 -怎么恢复
- We're gonna get him back. - How?
我们甚至连是什么让他变成这样都不知道
We don't even know what did this to him in the first place,
请你告诉我我们究竟该怎么做才能让他复原
so please tell me how the hell you and I are supposed to get him back.
每次我变身的时候 我都会去寻找
Every time I turn, I reach out,
我认为我会在那找到我的丈夫
and I think I'll find my husband there,
最后这都变成梦魇 失败告终
and this will all have just been some bad dream.
但这就是我们的生活
But this is our life.
这就是Josh的生活
This is Josh's life,
这让我开始感觉以后永远都这样了
and it's starting to feel like forever.
不要这样想 我们会找到解决方法的
Hey, come here. We're gonna find a way.
-你真的应该去洗个澡 -是的
- You really need to take a shower. - Oh, you bet I do.
Yeah
Yeah.
我以前从没有想过试试这个
I never thought to try this before.
这是唯一能使我放松的事
Yeah, it's the only thing that gets my knots out.
我真的喜欢上热石疗法了
I really got into the hot-stone treatments.
这起先并不舒服
It wasn't relaxing at first.
它让我想起太多死去的朋友
It reminded me of how too many of my friends died,
但经过十年左右的时间
but after a decade or so...
明天我们应该也这样做
We should do that tomorrow.
所以明天我们还是会在这里吗
Hmm, so we're still gonna be here tomorrow?
难道不是吗
Aren't we?
我不知道 这取决于你
I don't know. It's up to you.
真是令我感到惊讶 你知道的 你居然对我这么好
It still surprises me, you know, how nice you are to me.
我不会称之为对你好
Hmm... I wouldn't call it "nice."
我情愿称之为耐心
I'd say "patient."
结果我们成这德行了
Well, yet here we are,
被衣不蔽体的小妞们扔来扔去
letting scantily clad ladies throw us around on the ground,
不过这还挺有趣的
and it's kind of fun.
哦 踩到噗噗鸭了
Oh, it's a gas.
这个别致的地方真是非常不错的选择
This particular venue is a very good choice.
干得好
Well done.
不是我让我们到这里来的
I didn't bring us here.
不 是我让我们来到这里的
No, I brought us here,
但是你把这里变成现在这样的
but you made "here" this.
我们各做了一半的事
We're kind of 50/50 that way.
不是我变的
I didn't make this.
我又不是赫敏小魔女
I'm not Hermione frickin' Granger.
我没说你把这儿弄得很好
I didn't say you made it well.
我更喜欢你以前那个朴素的房间
I liked your rustic room on Lago de Como better,
不管怎样 我们都在这
but here are.
我之前做过这样的事么
I've done this before?
我们以前干过所有这样的事
We've done all of this before.
事情就是这样的
This is the way it goes...
你震惊了 我就跟你解释
You freak out, I explain things,
你就制造出了一个快乐的地方
you make a happy place.
你很擅长这个
Got it down to a science.
-什么 -是的 小甜心
- What? - Yes, sweetie.
你看 我对这里感觉很好
See, I was fine with here as just the way it was,
但是你想出去
but you wanted out.
我懂的
Look, I get it.
我有好几个世纪来面对我活在借来的时间这个事实
I've had centuries to face the fact that I'm living on borrowed time.
但是你 你很坚强
But you, you're tenacious.
但是这感觉...
But it feels...
这种感觉像是真的
It feels real.
你只是不想思考我们到底在哪
You just don't wanna think about where we are.
前期：  littlesnaka
我欲为人
翻译：  今夜梦醒何处   zhengyunyi823
翻译：littlesnaka  VampireNight
校对：魔王  VampireNight  半月
第四季 第一集
后期：青檬肉孜
本字幕由非人类字幕组原创制作 欢迎加入 QQ群20487648
终于见到你了
It's you.
嗨
Hi.
我们有多长时间
How long do we have?
可能三十分钟吧
Maybe 30 minutes.
让我们去外面
Let's get out of here.
我很高兴再次解释这个
I'm happy to explain it again.
这就像睡前小故事
It's like a bedtime story.
有时候我们都在熟悉的地方打瞌睡
Sometimes we both doze off during the familiar parts.
不 我知道我们被关联在一起
Yeah. No, I understand that we're connected.
你吃了我 我反抗了你
You ate me. I broke you.
我所不明白的是
What I don't understand
为什么你把我拖进这个兔子洞一样的地方
is why you would drag me down this particular rabbit hole.
为了拯救世界
To save the world.
啥 好吧
Ah! OK, yeah.
这真是一个用我衬托的正面英雄形象
That's a really healthy ego you got over there.
有没有人告诉你能成为一个优秀的邪恶领导人
Has anyone ever told you you'd make a fantastic cult leader?
我是认真的
I'm serious!
只有有限的次数你可以在
There are only so many times you can go around
全部的东西分崩离析之前
popping holes in the universe
在宇宙的漏洞附近乱逛
before the whole thing falls to pieces.
让我明白我在滥用力量
It's taken too many centuries and too many souls
牺牲了太多的时间和灵魂
for me to understand that I've abused my power.
你知道吗 不管你喜不喜欢 亲爱的 你也是一样的
And you know what? Like it or not, sweetie, so have you.
因为我从你那里闯出了一条路
Because I ripped my way out of you?
-不 -那是幸存
- No! - That was survival!
不 那叫聪明
No, that was smart.
我们躲避了太多次死亡
We have dodged too many deaths.
所以这里给了我们一席之地
That's why it benched us.
你还记得我问你如果死亡地点被摧毁了会发生什么吗
Do you remember I asked you what happens if you destroy a death spot?
这就是会发生的事 不对吗
This is what happens, all right?
你可以把这认为是一种拘留室
You can consider it kind of a holding cell,
然后我们是罪犯
as if we're criminals,
事实上 我们就是
which, in fact, we are.
对了 如果有一个扰乱
Right, well, if there was such a thing
宇宙平衡规则的监狱这样的地方
as an "upsetting the balance of the universe" prison,
你会被单独关禁闭
you would be in solitary.
你不会和我分享一丝一毫
You would not be sharing a cell with me.
和你比起来我更像脑力罪犯
I am like a white-collar criminal compared to you.
我只是尝试去帮助别人
I'm just trying to help people.
你以为我从前是怎么告诉自己的么
What do you think I used to tell myself?
我知道你不想听
I know that you don't wanna hear it,
但是我们分享的东西远比你知道的多
but we share more than you know.
而且你有力量
And you have power.
在灵狱里乱来对你来说是不安全的
It is not safe for you to be driving blind topside.
这不是你能决定的
It's not up to you to decide that.
我承认我之前低估你了
I admit that I have underestimated you before.
但是你没有像某些人那样攻击我
But you do not strike me as the kind of person
那些有着完好无损的恐惧感 做事如履薄冰的人
who has a healthy dose of fear, which is required to take precautions,
想的比做的慢半拍是十分愚蠢的
or to, you know, think for half a beat before doing something really stupid.
你打算把咱俩在这儿关多久
And how long do you plan on keeping us down here?
永远
Forever.
或者等我找到了结咱俩的方法
Or till I figure out a way to end us.
开始了
It's starting.
我得走了
I should go.
早上等你
I'll see you in the morning.
我们不会有事的
We'll be all right.
我爱你
I love you.
我也爱你
你最后和你的谁在一起了
What's the latest with your people?
我的谁
"My" people?
他们安静的很诡异
They've been strangely quiet.
需要打疫苗的人也打了
Anyone who needed inoculations has got them,
病毒的事也按正常发展了
and the virus has run its course.
让Nora接受我是件很难的事
It's hard for Nora to look at me.
在第一个月过后 我变回了自己
After the first month, when I turned back into myself.
感谢上帝，终于结束了
"Thank God, it's over."
然而早上的时候
And then morning came...
狼的那部分又撕裂了我的肉身
and the wolf ripped me apart again.
我才明白 不要
And I realized, no...
我是在暴走列车上呢
I'm on a runaway train.
当我看见你和Nora的时候 出现了一种模糊的感觉
There are glimpses, when I understand, when I see you and Nora,
我知道那是你
and I know it's you.
然后我极力的退回去
And then I'm yanked back down.
但是我只是
And then I'm just...
一个野兽
the beast.
在上个月月亮升起的时候
So last month, when the moon rose,
当我紧拥Nora的时候
when I held onto Nora...
我
and I...
在接吻时亲到了她的泪水
tasted her tears when we kissed,
我才瞬间清醒了
that's when it all became clear.
没有人应该像我这样带着包袱生活
No one should have to live with a burden like me.
好吧
OK.
因此我请求你
And that's why I asked you.
不行
No.
-这就是原因 -不行
- And that's why. - No.
这就是我需要你杀死我的原因
That's why I need you to kill me.
我说了不行 没门
And I said no. No way.
那把银匕首 我知道你带着它
The silver knife, I know you keep it here.
-我带着它是为了预防紧急事件 -这就是紧急事件
- I keep it for emergencies. - This is an emergency!
我这是在救你们
I'd be saving both of you!
-什么 -你是怎么做的
- What? - How do you even do it,
让我像个废人一样
running me ragged while trying
然后你同时工作着 供着房子
to keep your job and the house at the same time?
还有Sally 也许她没事 也许她正在到处找你
And Sally, maybe she's fine or maybe she's trying to reach you.
嘿 等一下
Hey, wait a second!
但是她找不到你 因为你没在那里而是在和我一起浪费时间
But she can't, because you're out here, wasting your time with me!
Josh
Josh.
这就是紧急事件
This is an emergency.
别这样好么
All right?
我到底该怎么做
What am I gonna do?
很好 你只是想让我这样发泄一下
That's pretty cool. You were just gonna let me do it, huh?
兄弟 当你花费超过一世纪用来周密考虑如何自杀
Hey, man, when you spend over a century contemplating suicide,
你就会明白这些事
you learn to read these things.
Nora 她既坚强又勇敢
Nora, she's strong and she's brave,
但是如果没有你回到她身边的那份盼望
but without that hope that you will return to her,
她的人性将何去何从
where will her humanity go?
我明白 我明白
I know. I know.
但是你们俩又能包容我多久
But how long can the two of you contain me?
多久后我会逃的你再也追不上
How long until I outrun you?
如果 但愿不会这样 我威胁到了某人
If, God forbid, I endanger someone...
你会像你该做的那样对我么
will you be able to do what
you know you have to do?
我知道你的意向是好的
You have the best intentions, I know.
你尽力的去救Kenny
You tried to save Kenny.
但是他已经走远了
But he was too far gone.
也许很快我也会这样
And maybe I will be, too, soon.
Nora知道你现在的感受么
Does Nora know how you feel about this?
你和她谈过这些么
Have you talked to her about this?
我在晚上把她锁起来之前只有半个小时的时间和她在一起
I have half an hour with her before I have to lock her up for the night.
我没法和她谈这些
I can't talk to her about this.
抱歉 我看一下
Oh, just a second. I'm sorry.
-是Kat么 -是Kat
- Was it Kat? - Yes, it is Kat.
你怎么和她说的
What do you tell her?
你怎么向她解释你在哪儿
How do you explain where you are?
-这是个很重要的对话 -生命诚可贵
- It's a very important conversation! - Life is important.
你的生活是很重要的 任何类似于人类的生活
Your life is important, any semblance of a human life.
她不该遭受我们带来的痛苦 不管我们是个什么
She shouldn't have to suffer at the hands of whatever the hell we are.
谁说她在痛苦
Who says she suffer...
你错过了什么
What are you missing?
没什么 一个非常愚蠢的教员活动
Nothing. It's a stupid faculty thing.
她甚至都没想去 Josh 所以
She doesn't even wanna go to it, Josh, so...
这就是为什么她需要你
Yeah, that's why she needs you.
去吧 我不去
Just go, man. I'm not going.
-你必须得去 -我才不去
- You have to go. - I'm not gonna go.
-你得去营救她了 -我很明确
- You have to salvage this. - I'm definit...
我很好
I'm fine.
只是需要点时间适应一下
It just takes me a minute to acclimate you know?
而且你是个非常非常难伺候的吸血鬼
And you are very high-maintenance vampire,
我现在只是没精力了
and I just don't have the energy right now
懒得应付你的胡闹
required to deal with your nonsense.
我需要一个人呆着
I need to be alone.
下个月见
I'll see you next month.
我们会在那之前帮你修理好你的问题
Look, man, we're gonna fix you long before that.
-你是走还是... -好 好 我马上走
- You gonna go or...? - OK! OK, I'll go.
下个月见
I'll see you next month.
你是说损坏我的死亡地点
You're saying that destroying my death spot
会抹去我回家的路
erases my way home.
但是我们是连在一起的
But you and I are linked,
你把我从我的死亡地点拖了下去
and you dragged me down through my death spot.
那就意味着我能从你的死亡地点出去
That's gotta mean I get out through yours.
我觉得我得找到它
Well, I guess I gotta find it then.
看了吧 这就是为什么你属于这里
You see? This is exactly why you belong down here.
你不知道你在做什么
You don't know what you're doing.
不 我知道 这些都是我做出来的
But I do. I made all this.
这就意味着我能毁掉它们
That means I can take it all away.
我这么做是为你好
I'm doing this for your own good.
Sally
Sally!
Sally 别下去
Sally, no!
顾客们请注意
Attention, shoppers.
30秒后
A flash sale in the Ladies' wear department starts
女装区开始限时抢购
in 30 seconds.
魔鬼
Devil!
另一个魔鬼来诅咒我们
Yet another devil come to curse us!
发生了什么事
What's happening?
你不能与我们同行 我们先把你烧死
You will not walk with us, devil! We will burn you first!
愿上帝将死亡降临予你
May God strike you dead!
你这个不干净的东西
Thou unclean one!
滚出去 邪恶的女人
Out! Out, devil woman!
往后站 保护好自己
Stand back! Protect yourself.
你知道怎么摘下这个么
Do you know how to get this off?
不要看向魔鬼
Do not look on the devil!
好吧 那就别看 然后呢
OK, so no, then?
死吧 去死吧
Die, already! Die!
折磨她 巫婆 折磨她
Suffer, witch! Suffer!
Donna的死亡地点居然是个超市
Donna's death spot was in a Shopmart?
该死的邪灵
Nothing but evil!
巫婆
Witch!
忏悔吧
Repent!
去你的噪音
Screw this noise.
我做到了
I did it.
I did it!
我做到了 我做到了 我做到了 我做到了
I did it, I did it, I did it, I did it.
我做到了
I did it, I did it.
好了 现在我怎么回家
All right, how the hell do I get home?
Margaret 来这里
Margaret, come here!
你好 很高兴看见你
Hello. Nice to see you.
谢谢
Ah! Thank you.
你怎么样
Hey, how are you?
如果我能醉得不省人事就更好了
If I could inject this into my veins, I would be a lot better.
你刚刚和Whitman院长妻子聊得热火朝天啊
Uhhuh! Another scintillating conversation with Dean Whitman's wife.
我都不好意思打断你们了
I'm sorry to interrupt.
她让你参加她超酷的读书俱乐部吗
Did she get you to join her awesome book club?
她恨不得整个宇宙都知道
Her need to be the smartest person in the room
她才是最聪明的家伙
has reached epic proportions.
你打算多买一些她孙女的童子军饼干吗
Will you buy more of her granddaughter's Girl Scout cookies?
因为我能帮你杀掉一些竞争对手
'Cause I could murder some Tagalongs.
我说过我们会跟院长妻子合得来
I said that you and I would go with the Dean's wife
然后就可以和院长搭上话了
and talk to the Dean...
回神了 Aidan！
Earth to Aidan!
嘿!
Hey!
Whitman院长
Um, Dean Whitman.
好啊 当然
Oh, uh, yeah! Totally.
如果你能让我在外面单独呆5分钟
If you were to give me just 5 minutes alone outside,
等我回来 我能把Whitman院长的裤子都迷掉了
I will come back, and I will charm the pants off Dean Whitman.
还有他老婆的
And his wife.
真恶心
Gross.
Susanna!
嗨
Hi.
你的手镯很漂亮
I was just admiring your bracelet.
谢谢 这是我祖母留给我的
Oh, thank you. It was my grandmother's.
好像现在很流行
It's like one of those things that's so old,
这些复古的东西
it's back in style now.
我以前有个类似的
I used to have one very similar.
可惜搞丢了
I'm sorry now that I lost it.
我是Kat 历史系的
I'm Kat. History department.
我是Diana 我现在做些研究
Diana. I'm just doing some research.
哪个领域的
Oh, um, what area?
还没入门呢
I think I'm still circling that.
千万别让我的导师知道
Don't tell my thesis advisor.
你的约会对象看起来很甜蜜啊
Your date seems very doting.
Aidan
Oh, Aidan.
他真的很绅士
He is quite the gentleman.
话说 怎么突然就没影儿了
Granted, he suddenly disappeared, uh,
不过在系里聚会上我倒是可以容忍他时不时的发神经
but I'll allow some boorish behaviour at a faculty mixer.
不好意思 但我忍不住看你们两个
Sorry, but I couldn't help notice the two of you.
这里别的人都
Everyone else here is...
穿着粗花呢 引经据典地开玩笑
Wearing tweed, making jokes about Chaucer,
偷喝Whitman院长的好酒
stealing Dean Whitman's good scotch?
是啊 诸如此类
Yes, all of those.
我是新来的 还有些摸不到头脑
I'm new in town, so I think I still feel a bit at sea.
你应该多和我们一起玩 我正打算去找他
You should come hang with us. I was just about to go find him.
虽然我不能打包票
I can't promise you
Aidan不会时不时说两句古英语
that Aidan won't bust out the Old English, though.
他倒是挺喜欢聚会的
He does like a good party trick.
好 一会儿外面找你
OK, I'll see you out there.
好 晚些见
OK, bye.
找到你了
There you are.
不好意思我走开了这么久
Sorry I took so long.
是工作电话
It's just work called,
他们把我今晚调成了两个连班
and they turned my shift tonight into a double.
不会吧
Seriously?
你和Nora要么就是医院最好的护士
Either you and Nora are the greatest nurses of all time,
要么就根本没别人在那个医院工作
or no one else works at that hospital.
我们能力强悍
We are incredibly skilled.
我刚刚在跟一个很不错的姑娘聊天
I was just talking to this woman, and she was nice.
我还打算带她一起去院长那里呢
I was gonna drag her over to the Dean's table with us.
奇怪 她刚刚还在这儿呢
It's weird. She was right behind me.
来吧
Come here.
Susanna 怎么回事
Susanna, what... what is this?
我在这儿 宝贝 是我
I'm here, baby. I'm here.
我不明白
I don't understand.
这不好吗
Isn't it wonderful?
刚刚明明是Kat
Kat was right here.
我知道 她很可人
I know. She's lovely.
她好亲切
She's so warm.
我明白
I understand.
我全明白 想想我们的过去
I understand everything. Think of our history.
是我的错 我们遭受的苦难都是因为我的错
It's my fault. Everything that happened to us is all my fault.
我还没来得及告诉你
And I never had a chance to tell you how...
真的很对不起
that I am so sorry.
那是很久以前的事了 亲爱的
It's ancient history, my love.
都过去了
Ancient history.
别停下
Don't stop.
Aidan
Aidan?
Aidan.
Sally
Sally?
终于醒来了
There he is.
你得再跟我解释一遍
You're gonna have to explain this one to me again!
Aidan 认真地说 我不知道怎么合理地把这个解释清楚
Aiden, seriously, I don't how I can logically explain to you
我跳进了血池的漩涡
that I dove through a funnelling pool of blood,
莫名其妙地出现在女巫的死亡现场
I popped up through a witch's death spot,
然后又莫名其妙地跑到了超市
and then I was birthed into a Shopmart.
感觉你都快活了1001岁了 嗜血如命
You are, like, 1,001 years old and guzzle blood.
我还以为你能明白呢
I just figured that maybe you could go with me on this one.
-我只是觉得这太奇葩了 -是啊
- I'm just saying this is weird! - Yes, it is!
太疯狂了 Sally
It's crazy, Sally!
好吧 你回来了 你觉得有什么不同吗
OK, you're back, but do you feel different?
如果Donna说的是真的 是不是说
If what Donna said is true, does that mean...
我不能让你再说下去了 因为那是胡说
I'm gonna stop you right there, because that's crazy talk.
你跟我说3个月来你都在跟一个女巫
You just told me that you spent 3 months chatting it up
-在日间SPA中心闲聊 -是啊 我造出来的SPA中心
- with a witch in a day spa! - Yeah, I made that day spa.
显然我能弄出点东西来逃避其他一些事情
Apparently I make things to not think about other things.
所以要么你得了妄想症 要么你超强大 或者两者都是
So you're either delusional or you're very powerful or both.
-你还记得 -我回来了
- Do you remember... - I'm back!
我回来了 这才是我现在关心的
I'm back. That is all I care about right now.
好吧 你回来了 对！你回来了
OK, you're back. Yes! You're back.
你回来太好了 你回来我太高兴了
And it's awesome you're back. I'm happy you're back.
我知道！
I know!
但是如果Donna说的是真的 如果你不该出现在这里
But if what Donna said is true... If you're not supposed to be here...
那你在这儿就不安全！
Then it's not safe for you to be here!
我的天！我知道要相信一个戴头巾的女巫真的很容易
Oh my God! I know it's really easy to believe a woman with a head wrap!
-什么 -我只是说
- What? - I'm just saying,
为什么我们要相信她说的话呢
why would we believe anything she's saying at this point?
因为她没撒过谎 Sally
Because she hasn't lied, Sally.
好吧 真的 她没撒过谎 真的！
Well, exactly, she hasn't lied. Exactly!
我是说 没错 她根据自己的喜恶玩弄事物
I mean, yes, she manipulated events to her favour,
但在我看来
but as I understand it,
她一直直言不讳 不是吗
wasn't she always a straight shooter, sort of?
直接喷火 是的
Of fireballs, yes.
拜托 我就在你眼前
Look, I am here right now.
-我们终于能在这里聊天 -我不是说这个！
- We are here, talking finally... - That's not my point!
在我经历这么多事情以后 简直是个奇迹
Which, after everything that I've been through, seems like a miracle.
为什么我们不能往好处想想 而不是一直做最坏的打算
Can't we focus on endless possibilities instead of worst-case scenarios?
对！
Yes!
Josh在哪里
Where's Josh?
我知道他不在家 因为冰箱空了
I know he's not here, because the fridge is bare,
而且杂志也没被那个超级粉丝展示出来
and the magazines aren't in their crazy-person fan display.
我能看看他吗
Can I see him?
行
Yes.
真希望我们还能在一起多呆一会
I wish we had more time.
我知道
I know.
但我又不想你见我
I don't want you to see me, though.
我想你记住这样的我
I want you to remember me like this.
我承受不起再一次分离了
I can't say goodbye anymore.
我只想我们能做自己
I just want it to be us again.
我知道
I know.
我感觉就像辜负了你
And I feel like I'm failing you.
我知道我不该这么说
I know that I shouldn't say that.
我希望能找到答案
I wanna have all the answers.
但是我越来越害怕
But I'm getting scared.
我们会找到办法的
We'll figure it out.
好吗 我们风风雨雨都过来了
OK? We always do.
别担心好吗
Please don't worry.
你得走了
You should go.
嘿 Nora
Hey, Nora,
你肯定不会相信 我刚发现谁在咱们家作祟
you are never gonna believe who I just found haunting our house.
是呀是呀！
Aaah! Yep, yep!
天呐 嗨
Oh my God! Hi!
老天 真希望能抱抱你
Oh my God! I wish I could hug you!
你到底怎么了 到哪里去了
What happened to you? Where have you been?
说来话长
It's a long story.
Aidan把Josh和你之间的牛郎织女故事告诉我了
Aidan just told me your whole Ladyhawke situation with Josh.
我不知道能说些什么 说"难过"都太苍白了
I don't even know what to say. "Sorry" seems so useless.
我懂 唉
I know. It's, uh...
你想见见他么
Well, would you like to see him?
-好 -好
- Yeah. - Yeah.
-你说过我见不到Josh... -不 你可以见
- So, you're telling me I can't see Josh... - Yes, you can see Josh.
只不过在下个月圆夜才能见到真Josh
Real Josh, till the next full moon?
糟了！
That's crazy!
他不见了
He's gone.
Aidan！
Aidan!
大事不妙
Awesome!
我得去当诱饵了
OK, well, uh, I'm just gonna go be bait!
Nora我们可能需要用麻醉枪
Nora, we're probably gonna need the "trank" gun.
你看到他了么 看到他了么
Have you seen him? Have you seen him?
我找不到他
I lost him.
-老天 -Nora 你不该来这
- Oh my God! - Nora, you shouldn't be here.
没关系 他不会伤害我
No, he won't hurt me.
谁也不知道他会做出什么来
You don't know what he would do.
他只是受到了惊吓
He's just scared!
没错 他既害怕又孤独 被自己可能要做的事儿吓坏了
Yes, he's scared and alone and he's terrified of what he might do.
这就是为什么他希望我们杀了他
That's why he wants us to kill him!
-什么 -我又话多了
- What? - I probably shouldn't have told you that.
这就是你的解决办法
So that's what this is?
天呐
Oh my God!
Aidan
Aidan.
回撤 回来
Get back! Get back!
Josh
Josh?
Josh.
知道么
You know what?
我不会那么做的
I'm not doing this!
你来决定
It's your move.
住手
Stop!
怎么回事儿
So, what the hell?
不知道
I don't know.
不知道刚才是怎么了
I don't know what that was.
Sally 谢谢你
Sally, thank you!
她去哪了？
Where did she go?
- Sally!
大伙
Guys?
嘿
Guys!
这可是新状况
Well, this is new.
你真的不要命了么
Do you really wanna die?
嗨 Blake
Hello, Blake.
Aidan 好久不见
Aidan! It's been a while.
你来我的医院这想干什么
Hmm! What are you doing in my hospital?
知道么 规矩不复存在了
You know those rules don't exist anymore.
哦 你来教我规矩呢
Oh, look who knows Boston politics.
我知道你重掌大权
I'd tell you to take it up with the new regime,
但是我知道你不愿参与其中
but I know how you hate to get involved.
别紧张
Relax!
没人要重整V族大军
No one's building a vampire army.
我们只是受够了在野外玩球了
We've barely got enough for a bocce game.
我们只想恢复原状
We're just trying to get back to status quo.
好的 安静
OK, shhh!
你一开始是对的 我没兴趣参与
You were right the first time. I don't wanna be involved.
但是萨普父子丧葬社? 不会吧
But Sapp & Sons? Really?
你得承认 这是最干净的做法了
Well, you have to admit, it's really the cleanest way.
一家殡仪馆无可厚非
There's nothing wrong with a funeral home,
但是这一家 他家的掌柜必死无疑啊
but that particular one, everyone that's ever owned it is dead.
-你是例外 -我是例外
- Except for you. - Except for me.
谁让野心勃勃之人陷入了这等破事儿
How did someone so ambitious get stuck with the grunt work?
要知道 这也不是一无是处
It has its benefits. You should know.
你和Bishop开创了整个伪装蓝领的先河 不是么
You and Bishop originated the whole blue-collar cover, didn't you?
没错 花费了不少时间建立那个系统
Oh yes! And it took a long time to get that system.
我已经洗手不干了
Hey, look, I've washed my hands of this,
但是我还住在这里
but I still have to live in this city,
如果你们管理得好的话 至少我感觉上会舒服些
and I'd feel better, at least, if I knew it was being run right.
所以如果你想找我聊聊或找我帮忙
So if you ever need to talk or run some things by me,
我可以让你少走些弯路
I could spare you some of the mistakes.
正如我说的 好久不见
Like I said, it's been a while.
那是因为一切顺利
That's because things are going well.
本以为你视自由高于一切
I thought you'd value your freedom more than anything.
转化他们时间紧迫 所以
I've got a short window of time to turn them, so...
是的 知道么
Yeah, you know what?
我想这次 我们就袖手旁观好了
I think we're gonna let the clock run out on this one.
-Aidan -抱歉
- Aidan. - I'm sorry.
组建你的部队吧 我不在乎
Build your army. I don't care.
但看在我的面子上
But have some respect.
别在这里瞎搞
Don't do it here.
你欠我一个人情 伙计
You owe me one, pal.
晚安 Blake阿姨
Evening, Aunt Blake.
拜托别老这么叫我
I really wish you'd stop calling me that.
我可是会很伤感的 就这样
I'm sentimental. That's all.
有什么新闻么
Any news?
没什么要紧的
Nothing urgent.
我更新了你的日程安排
I updated your calendar.
很好 谢谢
Ah, fantastic! Thank you.
见到你父亲了今天
I saw your father today.
Aidan
Aidan?
-他该死的藏到哪里去了 -没问
- Where the hell has he been? - I didn't ask.
我深刻意识到我们不需要他了
I was under the impression that we didn't need him.
没错
We don't.
那 你告诉他了么
So, did you tell him?
他的小儿子已长大成人 统管波士顿?
That his little boy's grown up to run Boston?
没有
No.
好吧
OK, good.
我想以自己的方式告诉他
I'd like to tell him on my own terms.
对了 Blake
And Blake?
知道么 我讨厌跟你说这个
You know, I hate to have to keep telling you this,
但是 再用这种口气跟我说话
but really, if you keep using that tone with me,
你就吃不了兜着走
there are gonna be repercussions.
我想 你明白?
I think you know that.
是的 明白
Yes. Of course!
抱歉
My apologies.
很好
Awesome.
这是什么
What is this?
圣婴之血令吾等重生
The blood of the child revives us.
The blood of the child revives us...
不好意思打扰了
Sorry to interrupt.
我误打误撞闯进来 并非
I just sort of popped in here, and I'm not...
圣婴之血令吾等重生
The blood of the child revives us.
-求求你 不 放我走 求求你 -圣婴之血令吾等重生
- Please, no! Let me go! Please! - The blood of the child revives us...
-圣婴之血令吾等重生 -不 住手
- The blood of the child revives us... - No. Stop!
不
No!
我爱你
I love you.
早上好
Good morning.
我感觉我说了句意义重大的话
I would like to acknowledge that I just said some very loaded words,
我不想让事情变尴尬
and I don't want things to get weird.
没有 完全没有
No, nothing's weird.
我们又不是22岁的小年轻了 Aidan
Neither of us are 22, Aidan.
没必要拐弯抹角
We don't have to dodge the conversation.
有时候 当一个女人也经历 我刚刚拥有的清晨
Sometimes, when a lady has the morning that I just did...
你知道 一个美妙的
you know, like, a really super,
欲仙欲癫的清晨
bordering-on-outstanding morning...
有些话就脱口而出了
things can slip out.
是的 就这么自然流露了
All right, OK, so it just slipped out,
你心里却没这么想
and you didn't mean it.
还记得Nora婚礼之后的那个清晨么
OK, remember the morning after Nora's wedding?
记得
Yes.
我从我卧室醒来 半梦半醒间
I woke up at my place, half the night before in a forgotten haze.
或许跟只有五个宾客却有一整箱香槟
Probably had something to do with the unfortunate combination
这个奇怪的组合有很大关系
of a case of champagne and a 5-person guest list.
当我从宿醉中清醒过来
But when the fog of my hangover lifted,
第一眼看到的就是你的面孔
the first thing that I saw was your face,
这感觉真的很好
and it felt really good.
就是那个时刻 我知道我从喜欢
And that's when I knew that I had gone from falling...
变成了爱
to fallen.
所以 是的 我是认真的
OK, so, yeah, I meant it.
我爱你 Aidan
I love you, Aidan.
但是如果你还没准备好说同样的话 我就一直缠着你
But I'm not gonna cease to exist if you are not ready to say it back.
好了 我上午有课
OK, I have an early class.
先去淋浴
Uh, I am going to jump in the shower,
出发
head on out,
回头给你打电话
and, um, I'll call you later.
Aidan
Aidan.
是我
It's me.